Yale Center for British Art printed materials
Yale Center for British Art, Institutional Archives
Yale Center for British Art printed materials
1965-2018
A011
Yale Center for British Art, Institutional Archives
9
9 boxes
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of various materials produced by the Yale Center for British Art from 1965 to the present. The materials include calendars, event materials, exhibition booklets, educational pamphlets, and visitor guides, as well as documentation of YCBA publications and programs. "Calendars" documents the history of the Center through its regularly-printed calendar of events and exhibitions. "Events" contains invitations and programs for lectures, symposia, dinners, and other events. "Exhibitions" contains material published in relation to exhibitions, including brochures, informational booklets, and programs for events held in connection with exhibitions. Through these materials, the collection provides a record of the Center's activities and development from its conception to the present.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open without restriction.
Art, British; Yale Center for British Art
- General
  - British Art Studies
    - British Art Studies Flyer, 2015 (Box 1321, Folder 1)
  - Brochures and Visitor Guides
    - The British Art Center at Yale, 1979 (Box 1321, Folder 2)
    - Information Card, undated (Box 1321, Folder 3)
    - Information Pamphlet, undated (Box 1321, Folder 4)
    - Permanent Collection Map, undated (Box 1321, Folder 5)
    - Self-Guided Group Information Card, undated (Box 1321, Folder 6)
    - Visitor Guide, undated (Box 1321, Folder 7)
    - Visitor Guide, 1994 (Box 1321, Folder 8)
    - Visitor Guide, 2013-09 (Box 1321, Folder 9)
    - Visitor Guide, fall 2014 (Box 1321, Folder 10)
    - Visitor Information and Maps, undated (Box 1321, Folder 11)
  - Building Conservation
    - Closing Notice, 2015-2016 (Box 1321, Folder 12)
    - Reopening Materials, 2016 (Box 1321, Folder 13)
    - The Year of the Roof, 1998 (Box 1321, Folder 14)
  - Collections
    - Charles M. Kurtz and the Glasgow School, 1990-04 (Box 1321, Folder 15)
    - Department of Prints and Drawings, undated (Box 1321, Folder 16)
    - Elizabethan and Jacobean Portraits, undated (Box 1321, Folder 17)
    - In and Out of Love, 1997-02 (Box 1321, Folder 18)
    - Rare Book Collection, undated (Box 1321, Folder 19)
  - Educational
    - Children's Booklet, "Great British Art Search", undated (Box 1321, Folder 20)
    - Children's Booklet, "Light Givers", undated (Box 1321, Folder 21)
    - Children's Pamphlet, "What do you do at a museum?", undated (Box 1321, Folder 22)
    - Learning through Looking: A Report on Two Colloquia for High School Teachers, 1994 (Box 1321, Folder 23)
    - School and Teacher Programs, undated (Box 1321, Folder 24)
    - Spanish-language Community Brochure, undated (Box 1321, Folder 25)
  - Friends of British Art
    - Andy Goldsworthy: Three Cairns Tour, 05-04-2003 (Box 1321, Folder 26)
    - Card, undated (Box 1321, Folder 27)
    - Information Cards, undated (Box 1321, Folder 28)
    - MoMA, QNS, and PSI Contemporary Art Excursion, 16-03-2004 (Box 1321, Folder 29)
    - New York Excursion, 03-04-2006 (Box 1321, Folder 30)
    - Tour of Venice: Power and Piety, 08-09-2001-16-09-2001 (Box 1321, Folder 31)
  - Grants and Fellowships
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1988-1989 (Box 1321, Folder 32)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1989-1990 (Box 1321, Folder 33)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1990-1991 (Box 1321, Folder 34)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1991-1992 (Box 1321, Folder 35)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1992-1993 (Box 1321, Folder 36)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1993-1994 (Box 1321, Folder 37)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1994-1995 (Box 1321, Folder 38)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1995-1996 (Box 1321, Folder 39)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1996-1997 (Box 1321, Folder 40)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1997-1998 (Box 1321, Folder 41)
    - Fellowships in British Art, 1998-1999 (Box 1321, Folder 42)
    - Grants for Scholarships in British Art, 1999-2000 (Box 1321, Folder 43)
  - Membership Materials
    - Art Gallery Associates, undated (Box 1321, Folder 44)
    - Members of the Yale Art Museums, undated (Box 1321, Folder 45)
    - One Architect, Two Museums, Three Ways to Belong, undated (Box 1321, Folder 46)
    - One Legacy, Two Museums, Three Ways to Belong, undated (Box 1321, Folder 47)
    - Student Membership, 1996 (Box 1321, Folder 48)
    - Yale Center for British Art Free Membership, undated (Box 1321, Folder 49)
  - Publications Lists
    - Publications List, 1984-01 (Box 1321, Folder 50)
    - Publications List, summer 1985 (Box 1321, Folder 51)
    - Publications List, fall 1988 (Box 1321, Folder 52)
    - Publications List, 1995-1996 (Box 1321, Folder 53)
  - Yale in London
    - Information Booklet, undated (Box 1321, Folder 54)
- Calendars
  - Calendar, 1979-02-1979-05 (Box 1323, Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 1979-09-1980-01 (Box 1323, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 1980-01-1980-08 (Box 1323, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, 1980-09-1980-12 (Box 1323, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 1981-01-1981-08 (Box 1323, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, 1981-09-1981-12 (Box 1323, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, 1982-01-1982-08 (Box 1323, Folder 7)
  - Calendar, 1982-09-1982-12 (Box 1323, Folder 8)
  - Calendar, 1983-01-1983-08 (Box 1323, Folder 9)
  - Calendar, 1983-09-1983-12 (Box 1323, Folder 10)
  - Calendar, 1984-01-1984-08 (Box 1323, Folder 11)
  - Calendar, fall, 1984 (Box 1323, Folder 12)
  - Calendar, 1984-09-1984-12 (Box 1323, Folder 13)
  - Calendar, 1985-01-1985-08 (Box 1323, Folder 14)
  - Calendar, 1985-09-1985-12 (Box 1323, Folder 15)
  - Calendar, 1986-01-1986-08 (Box 1323, Folder 16)
  - Calendar, 1986-09-1986-12 (Box 1323, Folder 17)
  - Calendar, 1987-01-1987-08 (Box 1323, Folder 18)
  - Calendar, 1987-09-1987-12 (Box 1323, Folder 19)
  - Calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 1323, Folder 20)
  - Calendar, 1988-01-1988-08 (Box 1323, Folder 21)
  - Calendar, 1988-09-1988-12 (Box 1323, Folder 22)
  - Calendar, 1989-1990 (Box 1323, Folder 23)
  - Calendar, 1989-01-1989-08 (Box 1323, Folder 24)
  - Calendar, fall, 1989 (Box 1323, Folder 25)
  - Calendar, 1990-1991 (Box 1323, Folder 26)
  - Calendar, spring, 1990 (Box 1323, Folder 27)
  - Calendar, fall, 1990 (Box 1323, Folder 28)
  - Calendar, spring, 1991 (Box 1323, Folder 29)
  - Calendar, fall, 1991 (Box 1323, Folder 30)
  - Calendar, spring, 1992 (Box 1323, Folder 31)
  - Calendar, fall, 1992 (Box 1323, Folder 32)
  - Calendar, spring, 1993 (Box 1323, Folder 33)
  - Calendar, fall, 1993 (Box 1323, Folder 34)
  - Calendar, 1994-1995 (Box 1323, Folder 35)
  - Calendar, spring, 1994 (Box 1323, Folder 36)
  - Calendar, fall, 1994 (Box 1323, Folder 37)
  - Calendar, 1995-1996 (Box 1323, Folder 38)
  - Calendar, spring, 1995 (Box 1323, Folder 39)
  - Calendar, fall, 1995 (Box 1323, Folder 40)
  - Calendar, spring, 1996 (Box 1323, Folder 41)
  - Calendar, fall, 1996 (Box 1323, Folder 42)
  - Calendar, spring, 1997 (Box 1323, Folder 43)
  - Calendar, fall, 1997 (Box 1323, Folder 44)
  - Calendar, spring, 1998 (Box 1323, Folder 45)
  - Calendar, 1999-01-1999-08 (Box 1323, Folder 46)
  - Calendar, 1999-09-1999-12 (Box 1323, Folder 47)
  - Calendar, 2000-01-2000-04 (Box 1323, Folder 48)
  - Calendar, 2000-05-2000-08 (Box 1323, Folder 49)
  - Calendar, 2000-09-2000-12 (Box 1323, Folder 50)
  - Calendar, 2001-01-2001-04 (Box 1323, Folder 51)
  - Calendar, 2001-05-2001-08 (Box 1323, Folder 52)
  - Calendar, 2001-09-2001-12 (Box 1323, Folder 53)
  - Calendar, 2002-01-2002-04 (Box 1323, Folder 54)
  - Calendar, 2002-05-2002-08 (Box 1323, Folder 55)
  - Calendar, 2002-09-2002-12 (Box 1323, Folder 56)
  - Calendar, 2003-01-2003-04 (Box 1323, Folder 57)
  - Calendar, summer, 2003 (Box 1323, Folder 58)
  - Calendar, fall, 2003 (Box 1323, Folder 59)
  - Calendar, 2004-01-2004-04 (Box 1323, Folder 60)
  - Calendar, 2004-05-2004-08 (Box 1323, Folder 61)
  - Calendar, 2004-09-2004-12 (Box 1323, Folder 62)
  - Calendar, 2005-01-2005-04 (Box 1323, Folder 63)
  - Calendar, 2005-05-2005-08 (Box 1323, Folder 64)
  - Calendar, 2005-09-2005-12 (Box 1322, Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 2006-01-2006-04 (Box 1322, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 2006-05-2006-08 (Box 1322, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, 2006-09-2006-10 (Box 1322, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 2006-09-2006-12 (Box 1322, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, 2007-01-2007-02 (Box 1322, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, 2007-01-2007-04 (Box 1322, Folder 7)
  - Calendar, 2007-05-2007-08 (Box 1322, Folder 8)
  - Calendar, 2007-09-2007-12 (Box 1322, Folder 9)
  - Calendar, 2008-01-2008-04 (Box 1322, Folder 10)
  - Calendar, 2008-05-2008-08 (Box 1322, Folder 11)
  - Calendar, 2008-09-2008-12 (Box 1322, Folder 12)
  - Calendar, 2009-01-2009-04 (Box 1322, Folder 13)
  - Calendar, summer, 2009 (Box 1322, Folder 14)
  - Calendar, 2009-05-2009-08 (Box 1322, Folder 15)
  - Calendar, fall, 2009 (Box 1322, Folder 16)
  - Calendar, 2009-09-2009-12 (Box 1322, Folder 17)
  - Calendar, 2010-01-2010-04 (Box 1322, Folder 18)
  - Calendar, 2010-05-2010-08 (Box 1322, Folder 19)
  - Calendar, 2010-09-2010-12 (Box 1322, Folder 20)
  - Calendar, 2011-01-2011-04 (Box 1322, Folder 21)
  - Calendar, 2011-05-2011-08 (Box 1322, Folder 22)
  - Calendar, 2011-09-2011-12 (Box 1322, Folder 23)
  - Calendar, 2012-01-2012-05 (Box 1322, Folder 24)
  - Calendar, 2012-05-2012-08 (Box 1322, Folder 25)
  - Calendar, 2012-09-2012-12 (Box 1322, Folder 26)
  - Calendar, 2013-01-2013-04 (Box 1322, Folder 27)
  - Calendar, 2013-05-2013-08 (Box 1322, Folder 28)
  - Calendar, 2013-09-2013-12 (Box 1322, Folder 29)
  - Calendar, 2014-01-2014-04 (Box 1322, Folder 30)
  - Calendar, 2014-05-2014-08 (Box 1322, Folder 31)
  - Calendar, 2014-09-2014-12 (Box 1322, Folder 32)
  - Calendar, 2015-01-2015-06 (Box 1322, Folder 33)
  - Calendar, 2015-07-2015-12 (Box 1322, Folder 34)
  - Calendar, 2016-01-2016-04 (Box 1322, Folder 35)
  - Calendar, 2016-05-2016-08 (Box 1322, Folder 36)
  - Calendar, 2016-09-2016-12 (Box 1322, Folder 37)
  - Calendar, 2017-01-2017-04 (Box 1322, Folder 38)
  - Calendar, 2017-05-2017-08 (Box 1322, Folder 39)
  - Calendar, 2017-09-2017-12 (Box 1322, Folder 40)
  - Calendar, 2018-01-2018-04 (Box 1322, Folder 41)
  - Calendar, 2018-05-2018-08 (Box 1322, Folder 42)
  - Calendar, 2018-09-2018-12 (Box 1322, Folder 43)
- Events
  - British Art Center Holiday Party, undated (Box 1325, Folder 1)
  - Concert Series: Fall, undated (Box 1325, Folder 2)
  - Dinner: In honor of Paul Mellon, undated (Box 1325, Folder 3)
  - Fall Film Series, undated (Box 1325, Folder 4)
  - Lecture: Arundel Castle: Ducal Splendor Revived, by John Martin Robinson, undated (Box 1325, Folder 5)
  - Lecture: Drawing in Isolation, Rebecca Salter, undated (Box 1325, Folder 6)
  - Yale Center for British Art Inauguration, 1977-04-16 (Box 1325, Folder 7)
  - Performance: Museum Pieces IV or Dances for a Building, 1979-04-22 (Box 1325, Folder 8)
  - Symposium: John Ruskin, 1983-09-24 (Box 1325, Folder 9)
  - Symposium: Recent British Cinema, 1984-02-18 (Box 1325, Folder 10)
  - Lectures: Constable, by John Steer & Michael Rosenthal, 1984-04-10-1984-05-01 (Box 1325, Folder 11)
  - British Art and Yale University: The Last Two Decades, 1985-03-08 (Box 1325, Folder 12)
  - Aspects of Art and Society in Eighteenth-Century England, 1985-06-30-1985-07-28 (Box 1325, Folder 13)
  - The Thirties in Britain: Concert and Symposium, 1986-02-28-1986-03-01 (Box 1325, Folder 14)
  - British Avant-Guarde Film, 1986-11-07-1986-11-08 (Box 1325, Folder 15)
  - Interdisciplinary Program: Wordsworth and the Borders of Romanticism, 1987-11-13-1987-11-15 (Box 1325, Folder 16)
  - Summer Program for Adults at the Yale Center for British Art, 1988-06-20-1988-06-24 (Box 1325, Folder 17)
  - The Culture of Restoration England, 1989-04-22-1989-04-23 (Box 1325, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: Matisse and the Chapel of the Rosary at Vence, by John Golding, 1989-09-19 (Box 1325, Folder 19)
  - Byron and the Drama of Romanticism, 1990-03-30-1990-04-01 (Box 1325, Folder 20)
  - Northeast American Society for Eighteenth-Century Studies Seventeenth Annual Conference: Envisioning the Eighteenth Century, 1993-09-30-1993-10-03 (Box 1325, Folder 21)
  - Historians of British Art, 1994-02-19-1994-02-20 (Box 1325, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: Aesthetes and Xenophobes: The Struggle for German Pictures at the British National Gallery, by Neil MacGregor, 1994-02-24 (Box 1325, Folder 23)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: The Dispersal of the Collections of King Charles I and His Courtiers, by Francis Haskell, 1994-10-1994-11 (Box 1325, Folder 24)
  - The British New Wave: Reconfiguring Modern British Cinema, 1995-04-08 (Box 1325, Folder 25)
  - Farewell Party: Duncan and Lisa Robinson, 1995-05-31 (Box 1325, Folder 26)
  - Jonathan Swift (1667-1775) symposium, 1995-09-22-1995-09-23 (Box 1325, Folder 27)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lectures: "The Late King's Goods": The Dispersal of the Collections of King Charles I and his Courtiers, by Francis Haskell, 1995-10-09-1995-10-25 (Box 1325, Folder 28)
  - A Symposium in Honor of Jules David Prown, 1995-10-20-1995-10-22 (Box 1325, Folder 29)
  - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies (INCS) Eleventh Annual Conference: The Exhibition of Cultures: Nineteenth Century Theory and Practice, 1996-04-11-1996-04-13 (Box 1325, Folder 30)
  - The Faerie Queen in the World, 1596-1996: Edmund Spenser among the Disciplines, 1996-09-26-1996-09-28 (Box 1325, Folder 31)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Modern Life and Modern Subject, by Lisa Tickner, 1997-01-28-1997-01-30 (Box 1325, Folder 32)
  - Symposium: The Future of the Past: Former Directors Look Backwards and Forwards, 1997-04-15 (Box 1325, Folder 33)
  - Queen Victoria, Home, and Empire: A Celebration of the Diamond Jubilee, 1997-10-04 (Box 1325, Folder 34)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lectures: Private Collection into Public Museum: Four Great Collectors, 1998-04-01-1998-04-22 (Box 1325, Folder 35)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Painting in English: The Making of the British School, by William Vaughan, 1999-03-23-1999-03-25 (Box 1325, Folder 36)
  - Sculpture Unveiling: Langlands & Bell: Opening/Capture, 1999-10-06 (Box 1325, Folder 37)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lectures: The Artist and the Garden, by Roy Strong, 1999-11-09-1999-11-18 (Box 1325, Folder 38)
  - Vita and Virginia, 2000-06-20-2000-06-21 (Box 1325, Folder 39)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Brilliant Effects: Jewels in English Art 1700-1850, by Marcia Pointon, 2001-03-20-2001-03-23 (Box 1325, Folder 40)
  - White Hassle, 2001-09-19 (Box 1325, Folder 41)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lectures: Masterpieces, 2001-10-03-2001-10-24 (Box 1325, Folder 42)
  - Curators and Canapes, 2001-10-12 (Box 1325, Folder 43)
  - William Walton: A Centenary Celebration at Yale University, 2002-10-18-2002-10-19 (Box 1325, Folder 44)
  - Andrew Forge Memorial Service, 2002-11-11 (Box 1325, Folder 45)
  - Psalm 150, 2003-04-06 (Box 1325, Folder 46)
  - My Architect: A Son's Journey, film screening, 2003-04-23 (Box 1325, Folder 47)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Brilliant Effects: Jewelry and its Images in English Visual Culture, 1700-1880, by Marcia Pointon, 2004-01-27-2004-01-29 (Box 1325, Folder 48)
  - The Restorer's Work: Thoughts about Paintings Conservation, 2004-04-07 (Box 1325, Folder 49)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: Antony Gormley: Making Space, 2004-11-04 (Box 1325, Folder 50)
  - Off the Beaten Track: Three Centuries of British Women Travellers, 2005-03-01 (Box 1325, Folder 51)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: The Epic of Common Life: Genre Painting and Social Change in Early Nineteenth-Century Britain, by David Solkin, 2005-04-12-2005-04-20 (Box 1325, Folder 52)
  - Wendy Sharp Duo concert, 2005-06-13 (Box 1325, Folder 53)
  - A Summer Institute for Teachers of Grades K-6, 2005-07-11-2005-07-14 (Box 1325, Folder 54)
  - Inside/Out, 2005-09-24-2005-09-25 (Box 1325, Folder 55)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: An Evening with Andy Goldsworthy, 2006-02-15 (Box 1325, Folder 56)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: Collectors, Benefactors, Scholarship, and the Public: The Role of a University Art Gallery, by Deborah Swallow, 2006-03-23 (Box 1325, Folder 57)
  - Book Launch and Panel Discussion: Art History: A Critical Introduction to its Methods, 2006-03-30 (Box 1325, Folder 58)
  - Look! Look! Look! Family Funday and Book Signing, 2006-04-02 (Box 1325, Folder 59)
  - Open House, 2006-09-07 (Box 1325, Folder 60)
  - Open House: Yale Graduate and Professional School Open House, 2006-09-14 (Box 1325, Folder 61)
  - Moggerhanger: A Soane Masterpiece Unveiled + Revealing Kew Palace: A Royal Retreat 1729-1818, lectures, 2006-11-06-2006-11-14 (Box 1325, Folder 62)
  - Andrew W. Mellon: An American Life lecture series, by David Cannadine, 2006-11-28-2006-11-30 (Box 1325, Folder 63)
  - Retirement Celebration: Judith Colton, 2006-12-10 (Box 1325, Folder 64)
  - Spring 2007 Soane Seminars: Inigo Jones: Architect, Stage Designer, 2007-03-12-2007-03-14 (Box 1325, Folder 65)
  - New Perspectives on the Panorama symposium, 2007-03-30-2007-03-31 (Box 1325, Folder 66)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: For an Excellent Purpose: Museums and their Publics in Britain from 1850 to 1914, by Giles Waterfield, 2007-04-03-2007-04-11 (Box 1325, Folder 67)
  - Undergraduate Student Open House, 2007-09-13 (Box 1325, Folder 68)
  - Yale Art Museums Graduate and Professional School Open House, 2007-09-20 (Box 1325, Folder 69)
  - Lecture and Book Signing: Moving Rooms: From Britain to the USA, A Trade in Architectural Salvages, by John Harris, 2007-11-28 (Box 1325, Folder 70)
  - Publication Celebration: Politics, Transgression, and Representations at the Court of Charles II, 2008-03-10 (Box 1325, Folder 71)
  - Lecture: Classicism in Color: The Country Houses of Robert Adam, by Eileen Harris, 2008-04-01 (Box 1325, Folder 72)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lectures: Rescuing Da Vinci; History of Matzah: The Story of the Jews, 2008-04-17-2008-04-24 (Box 1325, Folder 73)
  - Movie Screening: Gilbert & George (U.S. premiere), 2008-10-02 (Box 1325, Folder 74)
  - Lecture: Grayson Perry: My Civilization, 2008-11-05 (Box 1325, Folder 75)
  - Lecture and Book Signing: Extraordinary Ornaments: The Paintings of Richard Parkes Bonington, by Patrick Noon, 2008-11-13 (Box 1325, Folder 76)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Pen and Pencil: Writing and Painting in England, 1750-1850, Duncan Robinson, 2009-04-14-2009-04-28 (Box 1325, Folder 77)
  - Yale Art Museums' Fifth Annual Open House, 2009-09-03 (Box 1325, Folder 78)
  - Undergraduate Student Open House, 2010-09-02 (Box 1325, Folder 79)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: The National Gallery and the English Renaissance of Art, by Elizabeth Prettejohn, 2011-04-07-2011-04-27 (Box 1325, Folder 80)
  - Yale Art Museums Annual Open House, 2011-09-01 (Box 1325, Folder 81)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: The Production and Reproduction of a Monument: The Sanchi Stupa in Colonial and Postcolonial India, by Tapati Guha-Thakurta, 2011-11-09 (Box 1325, Folder 82)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: China and the Making of Modern India: A Story of Fantasy, Abuse, and Recovered Memory, by Amitav Ghosh, 2012-04-19 (Box 1325, Folder 83)
  - Brian Allen retirement celebration, 2012-05-01 (Box 1325, Folder 84)
  - Lecture: The Company of Artists: The Origins of the Royal Academy of Arts in London, by Charles Saumarez Smith, 2012-10-22 (Box 1325, Folder 85)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Memorial Lecture: The Cosmopolitanism of the Museum, by Kwame Anthony Appiah, 2013-04-09 (Box 1325, Folder 86)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Painters and Players from William Hogarth to Lawrence Olivier, by Robin Simon, 2013-04-10-2013-04-24 (Box 1325, Folder 87)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Sculpture on the Threshold: An Inquiry into the Underlying Forms of Sculpture, by Penelope Curtis, 2015-04-16-2015-04-30 (Box 1325, Folder 88)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture: Thomas Cole's Journey: Atlantic Crossings and Nineteenth-Century Landscape Painting, by Tim Barringer, 2016-10-05 (Box 1325, Folder 89)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture Series: Searching for the Young Soul Rebels: Style, Music, and Art in London, 1956-1969, by Thomas Crow, 2017-03-28-2017-04-12 (Box 1325, Folder 90)
  - Andrew Carnduff Ritchie Lecture: The Sea, The Sea: Hilton Als on Celia Paul, 2018-04-03 (Box 1325, Folder 91)
  - Symposium: Is This Permanence: Preservation of Born-digital Artists' Archives, 2018-05-11 (Box 1325, Folder 92)
  - Paul Mellon Lecture: Ruskin and the Idea of the Museum, by Tristram Hunt, 2018-10-24 (Box 1325, Folder 93)
- Exhibitions
  - Painting in England 1700-1850, 1965-04-15-1965-06-20 (Box 1318, Folder 1)
  - Seascapes, 1977-10-21-1978-04-16 (Box 1318, Folder 2)
  - The Cottage of Content, 1977-11-02-1977-12-31 (Box 1318, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife in British Art, 1978-01-19-1978-03-20 (Box 1318, Folder 4)
  - The British View of India, 1978-09-21-1978-12-03 (Box 1318, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Bewick: Artist and Naturalist, 1753-1828, 1978-11-17-1979-01-14 (Box 1318, Folder 6)
  - The Fuseli Circle in Rome: Early Romantic Art of the 1770s, 1979-09-12-1979-11-11 (Box 1318, Folder 7)
  - Painters and Engraving: The Reproductive Print from Hogarth to Wilkie, 1980-03-26-1980-06-22 (Box 1318, Folder 8)
  - The Camden Town Group, 1980-04-16-1980-06-26 (Box 1318, Folder 9)
  - The Art of Alexander and John Robert Cozens, 1980-09-17-1980-11-16 (Box 1318, Folder 10)
  - The Conversation Piece: Arthur Devis and His Contemporaries, 1753-1828, 1980-10-10-1980-11-30 (Box 1318, Folder 11)
  - Stanley Spencer: A Modern Visionary, 1981-01-21-1981-03-22 (Box 1318, Folder 12)
  - Turner and the Sublime, 1981-02-11-1981-04-19 (Box 1318, Folder 13)
  - Shakespeare and British Art, 1981-04-23-1981-07-05 (Box 1318, Folder 14)
  - Works of Splendor and Imagination: Exhibition Watercolors 1770-1870, 1981-09-16-1981-11-22 (Box 1318, Folder 15)
  - Eight Figurative Painters, 1981-10-14-1982-01-03 (Box 1318, Folder 16)
  - The English Miniature, 1981-12-16-1982-02-14 (Box 1318, Folder 17)
  - Painting in Focus: The Allegory of the Tudor Succession: The Family of Henry VIII, 1982-01-27-1982-03-07 (Box 1318, Folder 18)
  - The Great Exhibition: A Question of Taste + The Substance or the Shadow: Images of Victorian Womanhood, 1982-04-13 (Box 1318, Folder 19)
  - The Substance or the Shadow: Images of Victorian Womanhood, 1982-04-14-1982-06-13 (Box 1318, Folder 20)
  - British Architectural Drawings, 1982-04-21-1982-05-30 (Box 1318, Folder 21)
  - William Blake: His Art and Times, 1982-09-15-1982-11-14 (Box 1318, Folder 22)
  - Presences of Nature: British Landscape 1780-1830, 1982-10-20-1983-02-27 (Box 1318, Folder 23)
  - BLAST: The British Answer to Futurism, 1983-04-02-1983-06-26 (Box 1318, Folder 24)
  - Richard Wilson + The Early Georgian Landscape Garden, 1983-04-19 (Box 1318, Folder 25)
  - Richard Wilson + The Early Georgian Landscape Garden + Vauxhall Gardens, 1983-04-23 (Box 1318, Folder 26)
  - Painting in Focus: Benjamin West's John Eardley Wilmot, 1983-09-13-1983-11-27 (Box 1318, Folder 27)
  - Rembrandt in Eighteenth Century England, 1983-10-19-1983-12-30 (Box 1318, Folder 28)
  - The Bancroft Collection of Pre-Raphaelite Art + The McCormick Collection of Victorian Art, 1984-01-10 (Box 1318, Folder 29)
  - Painting in Focus: John Scarlett Davis' The Interior of the British Institution Gallery, 1984-02-28-1984-04-22 (Box 1318, Folder 30)
  - Gainsborough Drawings, 1984-03-07-1984-04-29 (Box 1318, Folder 31)
  - The Critical Eye/I, 1984-05-16-1984-07-15 (Box 1318, Folder 32)
  - English Caricature: From the Beginning to the Present, 1984-09-12-1984-11-04 (Box 1318, Folder 33)